extremepie.com 2017-07-06

# Privacy Statement

Internet Fusion Ltd is committed to protecting your privacy. We only use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalised shopping experience.

No information collected by Internet Fusion will be sold, rented or loaned except as expressly stated in this Privacy Policy and consented to by you.

Any personal information provided to or to be collected is controlled by Internet Fusion Ltd, of: 

Internet Fusion Ltd,  
Fusion Way,  
Bolingbroke Road,  
Fairfield Industrial Estate,  
Louth,  
LN11 0WA,  
United Kingdom 

We will not collect any information about individuals, except where it is specifically and knowingly provided, for example, at the time of ordering. This data is referred to in this policy as 'personal information'. 

When you order, we collect personal information such as your name, e-mail address, delivery address, telephone number, credit or debit card number and the card's expiry date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order(s) and to notify you about the status of your order(s). 

We will also collect non-transactional data should you enter a competition, take part in a survey, request an e-newsletter or contact Internet Fusion or one of its other operating companies via email. 

At times we may use the information we collect to notify you about news and information or goods and services we think you may find of interest. At every point on the site where such personal information is collected, we give you the option to tell us if you do not want your personal information used in this way. If at any later stage you decide you would rather not receive such information please contact us on our [Contact Us page](https://www.extremepie.com/en-UK/contact-us/)

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf, (i.e. when fulfilling orders), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. Our contractors have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

We may share non-personal aggregate statistics (group) data about visitors to this site, sales and traffic patterns. However we do not sell or share any information about you as an individual user of this site.
